weichert.com 2005-12-31

# Real Estate Professionals - Weichert Realtors

  | 

**Weichert, Realtors and the affiliated companies of Weichert (“Weichert” or “we”)** recognize the importance of protecting the privacy of certain information collected about our customers and potential customers. This Privacy Policy was created in order to demonstrate our commitment to protecting our customers' privacy.

Weichert may gather information from a variety of ways, including, loan applications submitted by potential borrowers, forms requesting additional information about a property, product or a service provided by Weichert. Weichert also learns of statistical patterns that show preferences for certain properties, market areas and services. This type of information is used to offer better services to the users of the Weichert web site. For instance, we may use statistical information to develop better tools to assist home sellers in marketing their homes to specific buyers interested in properties that meet their requirements.

**Personally Identifiable Information Collected.** Depending on the products and services you are interested in we may collect personally identifiable information such as (i) your name, address, telephone number, email address, social security number, assets, employment and income; (ii) data based on your experiences with us, with other Weichert affiliates, and with other service providers, such as your payment history, transaction parties, insurance policy coverage and premium amount, and (iii) information from consumer reporting agencies, such as your creditworthiness and credit history. We maintain strict physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect all personal nonpublic information. We restrict access to this information to only those persons who need to know it in order to provide you with products or services. We do not seek to collect personal information from children under the age of 18. We believe that children under the age of 18 should obtain permission from their parents before providing any personal information to us via this website.

**Sharing Information.** Weichert may share certain information regarding our customers and former customers among Weichert affiliates only in accordance with our strict security standards and confidentiality policies, and applicable laws. We hold our employees and agents fully accountable for adhering to these standards, policies and laws.

From time to time opportunities arise that we believe will benefit our customers and former customers. On a selective basis, we may share your name, address, telephone number and email address with third parties, such as insurance agencies, home warranty companies and tax service providers, record storage companies, moving companies, and other businesses that provide services to home owners, to market financial and non-financial products and services that may interest you. We will only provide this information to companies making these offers available to you under strict confidentiality agreements. For instance, we may share certain information with our strategic business partners with whom we have agreements to help provide customers with Weichert One Stop Shopping Services, or with other companies which help us to conduct business, such as credit bureaus and businesses which provide account maintenance, analysis and servicing. We may also provide information to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law. If you do not want to participate in these opportunities, please refer to the Opt-Out Notice Section below to learn about how to opt out.

**Usage tracking; Collection of your IP Address.** Your IP address is a unique number used to identify your specific computer on a public network. Weichert may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, such as diagnosing problems with our server, to analyze consumer behavior and trends, and to audit the use of our site. IP addresses are not used to personally identify a customer and are kept anonymous. Weichert may use IP addresses to identify a customer when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with our site terms of use or terms of service, or to protect our service, site's, customers or others.

**Use Of Cookies.** Weichert may use "cookies" to track web site visitors. Cookies are small amounts of data that the visitor retains on their computer, which enables the visitor to go back to saved information from a previous visit. They are also used to tailor the navigation of the web site to be consistent with the visitor's preferences and to enable them to see their sales agent's contact information in some cases as they work their way through the web site.

**Links to Other Web Sites.** Please be aware that when you click on links that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to their respective privacy policy. While Weichert supports the protection of privacy on the Internet, Weichert cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site.

**Legal Disclosure.** Weichert may also disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating Weichert's terms of use or terms of service, or may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with any of Weichert's rights or property, other Weichert customers, or anyone else Weichert may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services.

**Privacy Policy Changes.** Weichert reserves the right to change the Privacy Policy at anytime. Any revisions to this Privacy Policy are effective upon the posting of the changes on our web site.

**Corrections.** To correct or update your information, the following options are available for changing and modifying information previously provided: (i) email _privacy@weichert.com ;_ (ii) call the following telephone number: (973) 605-1619; or (iii) write us at the address below.

**Contacting Weichert.** If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the collection of information on your use of the website, the practices of this web site, or your dealings with Weichert please contact us at:

Weichert, Realtors  
1625 Route 10 East  
Morris Plains, New Jersey 07950  
Attention: Systems Administrator  

**ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS.** By using this site, you signify your agreement to Weichert 's Privacy Policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THIS POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE. Your continued use of Weichert's and/or its affiliates' sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

EffectiveMarch [01], 2004  
  
---|---
